dickmorris.com 2011-12-24

# Privacy Policy at DickMorris.com

It’s very important to us that we maintain the trust and confidence of all our community members. We keep only the personally identifiable information you share with us, nothing more. We don’t sell or rent our mailing list to third parties. If you sign up for our mailing list, you can rest assured your email address will not be shared with third party bulk emailers.

### LEGAL INFORMATION

DickMorris.com has implemented the Principles in this Privacy Policy, which describes how we collect, use and share personally identifiable information (“PII”) we obtain.

DickMorris.com is a general audience web site, and does not knowingly collect PII from children under 13 years of age.

From time to time DickMorris.com may revise this Privacy Policy to reflect industry initiatives or changes in the law, our PII collection and use practices, the features of our web sites or technology. If we make revisions that change the way we collect of use your PII, those changes will be posted in the Privacy Policy and the effective date will be noted at the beginning of this Privacy Policy. Therefore, you should review it periodically so that you are up to date on our most current policies and practices. If DickMorris.com materially changes its practices regarding collection or use of your PII, your PII will continue to be governed by the Policy under which it was collected unless you have been provided notice of and have not objected to the change.

COLLECTION: COLLECTION OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION (“PII”) BY DickMorris.com. DickMorris.com collects personally identifiable information (“PII” — that is, information such as your full name, email address, mailing address or telephone number) only in order to create or enhance our relationship with you. When we collect PII from you, it is because you voluntarily submit the information to us in order to participate in activities like sweepstakes, contests, games, surveys, forums, subscription registrations, chats or bulletin boards, in connection with content or suggestions you submit to us or because you want us to furnish you with products, services or information. We may also obtain PII from third parties.

### Cookies

Cookies are small bits of information that the DickMorris.com web sites place on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies remember information about your activities on our site(s) and enable DickMorris.com to make your visits to our site(s) more enjoyable. For example, cookies can store your password for easy logon to a site you have previously visited, can save your preferences for a personalized home page or can track the items you have placed in your “shopping cart” during a visit to our online store. Information about your activities on DickMorris.com sites and other non-personally identifiable information about you may also be used to limit the online ads you encounter to those we believe are consistent with your interests.

### Advertisements

Third party advertisements displayed on DickMorris.com’s sites may also contain cookies set by Internet advertising companies or advertisers. DickMorris.com does not control these advertiser cookies and visitors to our web site(s) should check the privacy policy of the Internet advertising company or advertiser to see whether and how it uses cookies (see “Notice” below for more information on third party advertisements).

### Threatening and/or abusive communications

Notwithstanding the foregoing provisions, I reserve the right to collect, disclose, and publicize personal information about anyone who sends a threatening or abusive communication, in any format or by any medium, to me or my employees, contractors, or family members. I will not honor requests for privacy attached to such communications.

### Miscellaneous

Notwithstanding the foregoing, DickMorris.com reserves the right to transfer or assign the data collected from our users in the event of a merger, acquisition, sale, pending merger, pending acquisition, or pending sale. In the event of bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, DickMorris.com may not be able to control how my user data are disposed of.

This privacy policy may be revised from time to time. Please check this page periodically for updates. Your use of this site on any given date indicates your acceptance to the terms of this policy as of that date.
